[{"answer": "A couple of bloodhounds and we have Uncle my friend's Cabin", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Was I? No... not by a Bolshevik", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "He's a bad man. Sends people to that place", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " We like you, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Comrade my friend..", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Comrade my friend..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Comrade", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Comrade", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Why?... Why should you carry other people's bags", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Two thousand francs", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A day", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Love to", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Facing north... I'd hate to commit myself without my compass... Pardon me... are you an explorer", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No... I am looking for the Eiffel Tower", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I am interested in the Eiffel Tower from a technical standpoint", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Bad manners to point with your own... Here... the Eiffel Tower", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Here... here we are... here you are and here I am... feel it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That proletarian! In the old days we'd have had her flogged", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You just told me you hadn't seen her", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Very well, monsieur.  Then, may I suggest an omelet with mushrooms", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " But, madame! If you don't think about food what do you think about", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Pardon me for addressing you but you insulted him, you know that. You hurt his feelings. It was just like telling a musician you don't like music. That good old man believes in food as you believe in my friend. You can't go around hurting people, Comrade my friend, but maybe you can make it up to him. Do you know how?  By eating everything with relish, by drinking everything with gusto, by having a good time for the first time in your natural life", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I didn't follow you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I always eat here", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " But my dear child, I am most at home among working men. I hate the places where you circulate", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Just an old man. His memory is getting weak", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Must one always be after something", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes, that place", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Yes, my friend, you did", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Quite right... yes, yes, yes, but first you're going in that door and you're going to take a little spirits of ammonia and lie down", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " No speech", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Are we going to build our little house", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Not white, darling", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No! No", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes... a kiss... salute", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why should an aristocrat want to go to that place", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What business", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "The Grand Duchess Swana... active in the White Russian movement", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "But you had", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "As beautiful as that? What else? Come, tell me", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Evening gown", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Evening gown", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What do you wear in the morning", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Good morning, Comrade Commissar. Here is my report on the materials available for trading in the next four months", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes, it does", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Don't ask for it, my friend. There is a Turkish proverb which says,", "docId": "Ninotchka.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "With our cream situation what it is, it is that place which should apologize to the cats", "qsentId": 48}]